<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Govardhan Puja 2017</eventname>
   <eventdate>10-20-2017</eventdate>
   <eventtime>06:30pm - 9:00pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>Govardhan Puja or Annakut puja (meaning a heap of grain), is celebrated on account of Lord Krishna defeating Lord Indra by lifting the Govardhan hill.  </eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>govardhan-puja-milwaukee.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>govardhan</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>Govardhan Puja or Annakut puja (meaning a heap of grain), is celebrated on account of Lord Krishna defeating Lord Indra by lifting the Govardhan hill. The puja is performed on the fourth day of the Hindu festival Diwali by worshiping the heap of grain that symbolizes the Govardhan mountain. Govardhan puja is celebrated to cherish the victory of Lord Krishna over the arrogant Lord Indra.</para1>
       <para2> Lord Krishna taught the people of Vrindavan to worship nature. Annakut pooja is performed with immense gratitude, passion and eagerness. It is one of the most important rituals followed across various states of India such as Punjab, Haryana, Uttar Pradesh, Mathura, Vrindavan and Bihar.</para2>
       <para3>Govardhan is a small hillock situated at 'Braj', near Mathura. According to the legends in 'Vishnu Puraan', people of Gokul used to worship and prepare a sacrifice to please Lord Indra as they believed that it was he who sent rains for their welfare. It has been a ritual for many  years. People believed that if they do not perform this puja, Indira would get angry and there will be no rain which will lead to scarcity of grains and fodder. </para3>
       <para4>Lord Krishna asked everyone not to follow the rituals blindly. Lord Krishna explained them that it was Govardhan mountain and not Lord Indra who helps bringing rain and hence they should worship the Govardhan. People got convinced and performed the puja for Govardhan. This made Lord Indra furious. He vented his anger upon the villagers of Vrindavan. He began heavy rains and villagers had to face heavy floods as a result of his anger. Lord Krishna came forward to ensure the safety of the villagers and cattle. After performing puja and offering prayers to Govardhan, Lord Krishna lifted the mountain on the little finger of his right hand so that everybody could take shelter under the hill. He lifted the hill for seven days and seven nights. After this incidence Lord Krishna was also known as Giridhari. Indra accepted him as a supreme power. Since then, Govardhan puja came into existence.</para4>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
