<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Lord Jagannath Rath Yatra</eventname>
   <eventdate>07-15-2018</eventdate>
   <eventtime>12:00pm - 02:00pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Sri Radha Madhav Temple</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>The Ratha Yatra or the Chariot festival is celebrated at the temple of Jagannath which is associated with God Jagannath. This festival is known as Rath Yatra, meaning the journey -yatra- of the chariots -ratha-. The Rathas are huge wheeled wooden structures, which are built anew every year and are pulled by the devotees.</eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>rath-yatra-milwaukee.jpeg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>rathyatra-2018</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>The Ratha Yatra festival is perhaps the oldest continuously celebrated spiritual festival in the world.  The chariot of 'Jagannatha', 'Balarama' and 'Subhadra' is splendidly decorated each year, and then pulled by crowds through the city streets.  People of all nations and faiths are invited to join in this festival "for the soul". It features huge, wooden chariot pulled by hand in a grand procession.</para1>
       <para2> Sequence of events.
         <![CDATA[
          <ul> <li> 12:00 pm - Procession Begins </li><li> Follow the procession for 1.1 mile (see Map below) </li><li> 2:00pm - Complimentary Feast - Prasadam </li></ul>
        ]]>
        Path of the Rath Yatra.
        <![CDATA[
          <img src="images/rathyatra-2018/rath-yatra-path.jpg"/>
       ]]>
      </para2>
      <para3>All the way through there is melodious singing, chanting and dancing to rhythmical drums and cymbals. The procession ends with a stage show, a festival and delicious vegetarian prasadam feast.</para3>
       <para4> We encourage all communities to participate and hope all kinds of public will attend. Dancing and chanting in the streets with tents full of free food, yoga, and kirtan and entertainments on main stage. Fun for the whole family. </para4>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
