<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Gaura Purnima</eventname>
   <eventdate>03-20-2019</eventdate>
   <eventtime>06:00pm - 09:00pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>Gaura Purnima, Gaura Purnima the appearance anniversary of Lord Sri Caitanya Mahaprabhu, who is Krishna Himself in the role of His own devotee. He appeared in 1486 in Mayapur, West Bengal.</eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>Gaura-Purnima-Header_0_0.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>gaurapurnima</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>Gaura Purnima the appearance anniversary of Lord Sri Caitanya Mahaprabhu, who is Krishna Himself in the role of His own devotee. He appeared in 1486 in Mayapur, West Bengal.
         <![CDATA[
         Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna, Krishna Krishna, Hare Hare/
         Hare Rama, Hare Rama, Rama Rama, Hare Hare]]>
       </para1>
       <para2> Following options are available  <![CDATA[
        <ul> <li> Aarti Plate - $11.00 </li><li> Abhishek - $21.00 </li><li> Dress Donation - $50.00 </li><li> Prasad Sponsorship - $100.00 </li></ul>
  ]]></para2>
       <para3>Chaitanya Mahaprabhu is the Supreme Person, Krishna Himself, appearing as His own devotee, to teach us that we can gain full enlightenment simply by chanting the holy names of the Lord.
         Gaura Purnima means "golden full moon," signifying that:
         <![CDATA[
         <ol>
           <li>Lord Chaitanya was “born” during a full moon, </li> and
           <li>The Lord blesses everyone with the soothing, moonlike rays of His sublime teachings.</li>
         </ol>]]>
       </para3>
       <para4>Those who witnessed Mahaprabhu's pastimes saw Him dance and chant with ecstatic love for God, the likes of which had never been seen before. He encouraged everyone to follow this same process. He taught that anyone—regardless of background or spiritual qualification—could develop their innate love of God and experience great spiritual pleasure by chanting the Hare Krishna mantra.</para4>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
