<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Nrisimha Chaturdashi</eventname>
   <eventdate>05-17-2019</eventdate>
   <eventtime>06:30pm - 9:00pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>Millions of years ago to please his dear devotee Prahlada and to kill the wicked demon Hiranyakashipu, Lord Nrsimhadeva appearred from a pillar.</eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>Nrisimha-chaturdashi.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>nrisimhachaturdashi2019</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>The great protector appeared with lions face and claws and the human torso. He is ferocious and terrifying for those who do not believe in Him but fiercely protects His devotees from any obstacles and harm that come their way. Unmatched and supreme He is present on earth and heaven and everywhere in between.</para1>
       <para2>Lord Narasimha is worshipped in all temples for He is knows to protect His devotees form all dangers.</para2>
       <para3> Want to donate, Following options are available  <![CDATA[
        <ul> <li> Aarti Plate - $21.00 </li><li> Abhishek - $25.00 </li><li> Dress Donation - $100.00 </li><li> Prasad Sponsorship - $251.00 </li></ul>
      ]]></para3>
       <para4>Hiranyakashipu received a special benediction from Lord Brahma that he could not be killed by any human being, demigod or animal or any other entities; he could not be killed by any kind of weapons, neither during day nor night. So, the Lord appeared in half-man half-lion form and killed him with His nails at twilight, thus satisfying all the conditions. </para4>
       <para5>Narasimhadeva appeared at dusk on the Shukla Chaturdashi (fourteenth day of the bright fortnight) in the month of Vaishakha (May). Devotees fast till dusk on this day. We invite you all to participate in the celebrations and seek the blessings of Sri Prahlada Narasimha.</para5>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
