<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Happy New Year 2020 Celebrations</eventname>
   <eventdate>12-31-2019</eventdate>
   <eventtime>06:30pm - 12:15am</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>2020 Wishes from Hare Krishna Temple Mission.</eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>happy-new-year-2020.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>happynewyear2020</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>As we all step into the new year 2020,  Hare Krishna Temple of Milwaukee, WI extends warm wishes to all the devotees. 
              At the Hare Krishna Temple, we will start the new year with Kirtan, singing and chanting the holy names of Shree Radha Krishna.
         <![CDATA[
           <h1>Events on the new year eve</h1>
        <ul>
         <li>Gaura Arati - 6:30pm</li>
         <li>Prasad - 7:30pm onwards</li>
         <li>Kirtan - 8:00pm till Midnight</li>
         <li>New Year Arati - 12:00am</li>
         <li>New Year Prasad - 12:15am</li>
        </ul>
          ]]>
       </para1>
       <para2>New Year Message From Temple <![CDATA[
         <strong> 
         <p>The essential ingredient for making life a success is inspiration.  
         It is the fuel that energizes us to exert our physical, mental, and intellectual faculties to the utmost.  It generates the enthusiasm that creates the vital edge in our performance.  
         Inspiration is thus the elixir of champions and the tonic of geniuses.  
         It enables us to wade through difficulties like a knife cuts through butter.  
         When we are inspired, we naturally lift our thoughts from the mundane to the sublime.</p>
         <p>
         The chance to top-up our fountain-source of inspiration to the brim has again presented itself in the form of New Year’s Day, 2020. 
         God has sewn a garland of 1.5 million priceless minutes, each studded with sixty jewellike seconds, and offered this necklace to us. 
         That is a lot of opportunities coming our way, for thinking wonderful thoughts and performing noble acts! 
         </p>
         <p>
         To enable us to make the most of the year ahead, God will empower our lungs to breathe 18 million times, while our heart pounds 40 million times and the blood in our arteries traverses 4.2 million miles.   
         Life is His gift to us; what we make of it will be our gift to Him. 
         Let us resolve to put in our very best efforts to please Him by rising above our frailties and developing divine virtues. 
         </p>
         <p>
         Like the year 2019 that went by, it is only natural to expect that the year to come will also bring a mixed bag of experiences. 
          As we go through 365 day-and-night cycles, we will also ride the roller coaster of victory and defeat. 
          But through these diverse experiences, one item will always remain independent of the external situation.  
          And that is the attitude we choose to harbor within towards the circumstances around us.
           Let us then choose to focus on solutions instead of problems.  
           Rather than waste priceless time and energy asking “Why?”, we will focus on “How?”, for that is the way to progress.  
           If life sends us a lemon, we will not be bogged down by the question “why” this happened to us. 
            Rather, we will think of “how” we can make a lemonade from it.
         </p>
         <p>  
         Best wishes for the New Year 2020!  Happy Bhakti Diwas!  
         May this be the most fulfilling year of your life yet. 
         </p>
         Your ever well-wisher,<br>
         Hare Krishna Temple 
         </strong>
  ]]></para2>
       <para3><strong>Get Involved with Hare Krishna</strong> We, at the Hare Krishna Temple,  wish all our readers a year filled with devotion and service to the divine.  </para3>
       <para4>Happy New Year 2020 !!!</para4>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
