<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Sri RamNavami</eventname>
   <eventdate>04-02-2020</eventdate>
   <eventtime>06:00pm - 9:00pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>Lord Sri Ramacandra is a powerful incarnation of the Supreme Personality of Godhead as an ideal king. He appeared in the Treta-yuga, more than two million years ago.</eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>ramnavami.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>ramanavami2020</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>Ayodhya is birthplace of Lord Rama and Rama Navami celebrations in Ayodhya are remarkable. Devotees come to Ayodhya from far-flung places. After taking holy dip into river Sarayu Devotees visit Rama temple to participate in birthday celebrations.
        <![CDATA[
           <h1>Events for RamNavami</h1>
        <ul>
         <li>Kirtan - 6:30pm</li>
         <li>Gaura Aarti - 7:00 - 8:00 pm </li>
         <li>Maha Abhishek - 08:00 - 09:00 pm</li>
         <li>Maha Aarti - 09:00 - 09:30pm </li>
         <li>Prasadam - 09:30 pm</li>
        </ul>
          ]]>
       </para1>
       <para2>Rama was the Lord Hari Himself, incarnate on earth for the destruction of Ravana. He was well accomplished, beautiful and endowed with royal marks. His glory and prowess were unlimited. He was peerless on earth. He was free from malice. He was gentle. He was the protector of all His people. He always addressed them in gentle words. He never used any harsh words even when somebody provoked Him. He held sway over the whole world.</para2>
       <para3> Want to donate, Following options are available  <![CDATA[
        <ul> 
        <li> Aarti Plate - $21.00 </li>
        <li> Abhishek - $25.00 </li>
        <li> Dress Donation - $100.00 </li>
        <li> Prasad Sponsorship - $251.00 </li>
        </ul>
      ]]></para3>
       <para4>One who approaches Sri Rama with love and worshipfulness becomes large-hearted, pure in spirit, good-natured and dispassionate in thought, word and deed. A true devotee of Lord Rama is His representative, with His power and His knowledge. </para4>
       <para5>Devotion to God is not a simple emotion. It is the result of intense dispassion and purity of heart and attitude. You should strive your utmost to possess the good qualities that are extolled in the Ramayana and exemplified in the life of Lord Rama. </para5>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
