<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Hare Krishna Kirtan, Lecture and Dinner</eventname>
   <eventdate>08-27-2016</eventdate>
   <eventtime>6:30 pm - 08:00 pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Prayer</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>Chanting the name of Krishna and singing his name followed by Aarti and Dinner... </eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>harekrishna-sunday-event.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>sundayevent</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>Chanting Hare Krishna awakens love of God. Chanting Hare Krishna brings liberation as a side benefit along the way.When you chant Hare Krishna, you automatically develop knowledge and detachment. Chanting Hare Krishna gets you out of the endless cycle of birth and death. It is the most effective means of self-realization in the present Age of Quarrel. Nothing else works nearly as well. </para1>
       <para2>All other Vedic mantras are included in the chanting of Hare  Krishna. So just by chanting this mantra, you get the benefit of all  others. Chanting Hare Krishna purifies not only you but every living entity  around you. Whoever hears the chanting gets spiritual benefit. A person who chants Hare Krishna develops all good qualities. You can chant Hare Krishna softly for personal meditation or loudly with your family or friends. Both ways work.</para2>
       <para3>It’s free. Chanting Hare Krishna never costs you money. Chanting Hare Krishna brings the highest states of ecstasy. There are no previous qualifications needed for chanting Hare  Krishna. Young or old, anyone can chant—from any race, any religion, or  any country of the world.
Even if you don’t understand the language of the mantra, it works anyway. Chanting Hare Krishna brings relief from all miseries.</para3>
       <para4>After chanting His Glory, dinner is served as prasadam. All are welcome.</para4>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
