<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Govardhan Puja and Diwali Celebrations</eventname>
   <eventdate>10-28-2019</eventdate>
   <eventtime>05:30pm - 08:00pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>Govardhan Puja and Diwali Celebrations, one of the auspicious festival is celebrated a day after the Diwali in the month of Kartik. Also known as Bali Pratipada, on this occasion, devotees offer puja to Lord Krishna.</eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>govardhan-diwali.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>govardhanpuja2019</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>Devotees perform this pooja by making hillocks of cow-dung which represents the Mount Govardhan. They decorate it with flowers and worship them. People also pray to Lord Krishna who taught people to worship the nature.
         <![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li>On Govardhan Pooja, people worship mountain as it provides shelter to the people under severe conditions.</li>
          <li>During the Govardhan Pooja, devotees bath their cows and bulls in the morning and decorate them with garlands and flowers.</li>
          <li>The Govardhan Pooja day coincides with Gujarati New Year day, which is celebrated on Shukla Paksha Pratipada of Kartik month.</li></ul>]]>
       </para1>
       <para2> Following options are available  <![CDATA[
        <ul> <li> Aarti Plate - $11.00 </li><li> Abhishek - $21.00 </li><li> Dress Donation - $50.00 </li><li> Prasad Sponsorship - $100.00 </li></ul>
  ]]></para2>
       <para3>It is mentioned in the Hindu scriptures, the observer of the Radha Ashtami vrat will be blessed with a prosperous and happy life. the person will overcome all his obstacles, attain the materialistic desires and finally attain salvation. It is believed that after observing the Radha Ashtami fast and worshipping Goddess Durga, the person will be freed from all their sins. Their minds will be cleared from negative and bad thoughts and he/she will attain spiritual bliss.</para3>
       <para4>Diwali ceremony can be observed in the temple by illuminating 100's of candles, in different parts of the temple, and offering special Prasad to the Deity. This ceremony was observed by the inhabitants of Ayodhya, the Kingdom of Lord Ramacandra, while Lord Ramacandra was out of His Kingdom due to His 14 years banishment by the order of His father. His younger step-brother Bharata, took charge of the Kingdom and the day on which Lord Ramacandra took back the charge again from His brother, and seated on the throne, this is observed as Diwali function. This is the original idea of Diwali, and Dipabali. Dipabali means the same thing—Dipa means candles, and bali means numerous. When numerous candles are lighted it is called Dipabali. In India, this Dipabali function is celebrated in a special auspicious occasion.</para4>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
