<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<event>
   <eventname>Gaura Purnima Festival</eventname>
   <eventdate>03-09-2020</eventdate>
   <eventtime>06:30pm - 08:30pm</eventtime>
   <eventtype>Free</eventtype>
   <eventphone>+1 414-763-2785</eventphone>
   <eventemail>contact@krishnatemplemilwaukee.org</eventemail>
   <eventcategory>Celebrations</eventcategory>
   <eventorganizer>Hare Krishna Temple Mission</eventorganizer>
   <eventaddress>2419, W RAMSAY AVE, MILWAUKEE, WI - 53221</eventaddress>
   <eventbdesc>Gaura Purnima Festival Holi Celebrations.</eventbdesc>
   <eventimg>gaurapurnima-2020.jpg</eventimg>
   <eventimgfolder>gaurapurnima-2020</eventimgfolder>
   <eventldesc>
       <para1>Gaura-purnima is a Vaisnava festival that occurs in March celebrating the birth of the saint Chaitanya Mahaprabhu. Gaura Purnima means "Golden Full Moon", a reference to Chaitanya.
       <![CDATA[
           <h1>Events on the new year eve</h1>
        <ul>
         <li>Gaura Arati and Kirtan - 6:30pm</li>
         <li>Abhishekh - 7:00 - 8:00 pm </li>
         <li>Bhoga offering - 8:15pm </li>
         <li>Maha Aarti and Kirtan - 8:30pm</li>
         <li>Prasadam - 09:00 m</li>
        </ul>
          ]]>
        </para1>
       <para2>Gaura Purmina is the appearance anniversary of Lord Chaitanya Mahaprabhu (1486-1534) who is Radha and Krishna combined. On this day, which is a full-moon day, everyone fasts till moonrise, and people visit the temple to see the Deities of the Lord in the temple room. The devotees present dramas and classes about Lord Chaitanya’s activities. The Deities of Gaura-Nitai receive new clothes, and the devotees engage in extra kirtan. At moonrise we serve a prasad feast.</para2>
       <para3>The Supreme Lord Sri Krishna appeared as Sri Chaitanya Mahaprabhu to establish Sankirtana (chanting of the Holy Names) – the Yuga Dharma for this age of Kali. He appeared on Phalguni Purnima, the full moon day in the month of Phalguna, (Feb-March) in the year 1486 AD (1407 Shakabda) at Sridham Mayapura as the son of Sri Jagannath Mishra and Srimati Sachidevi. His parents named him Nimai since he was born under a nimba (neem) tree in the courtyard of His paternal house. His appearance day is celebrated as Gaura Purnima.</para3>
       <para4></para4>
   </eventldesc>
</event>
